softwaretestingfundamentals.com 2016-06-29

# Privacy Policy – Software Testing Fundamentals

At **Software Testing Fundamentals** , we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important.

Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use our site, and how we safeguard your information.

**Log Files**

As with most other websites, we collect and use anonymous information such as the name of your ISP, browser used, connection speed, date and time of visit and the pages you access. This data does not allow for the specific identification of any particular user, but is aggregated with all other visitor information. The information is used to help improve the site, analyze trends and provide a better experience for our readers.

**Cookies**

This website may use cookies to track information relevant to affiliate marketing, advertising and to improve the user experience. You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites.

**Third party advertisements**

We also use third party advertisements to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers information including your IP address, your ISP, the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited.

**Links**

This site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of these other sites. We suggest you to be aware of this when you leave this site and to read the privacy statements of each and every site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this site.

**Google Specific**

****Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to your website.Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the[advertising opt-out page](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). Alternatively, users may opt out of a third-party vendor’s use of cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative [opt-out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

**Acceptance of this Policy and Concerns**

By using this site, you signify your agreement to the terms and conditions of this site’s Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to these terms and conditions, please do not use the site. We reserve the right, at our sole discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions of this policy at any time. If you feel that we have not followed this website’s stated privacy policy, please [contact](http://softwaretestingfundamentals.com/contact/) us.
